Guide to the Office of the President Records, Virginia B. Smith Files, 1950-2010 (bulk 1977-1986)
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
- Series IX. Additions
  - Laure Christian Ford — Interview, Dec 1983 (Folder 52.31)
  - Fourteen Meal Plan, 1980 (Folder 52.32)
  - Freshmen Dorm Visits, 1981 (Folder 52.33)
  - Freshman Norms, 1984 (Folder 52.34)
  - Freshman Norms, 1980 (Folder 52.35)
  - Foundations — General, 1979-1981 (Folder 52.36)
  - Fulbright Visiting Professor, 1980-1982 (Folder 52.37)
  - Gifts (Major), 1980-1981 (Folder 52.38)
  - Gifts — Miscellaneous and Anonymous, 1979-1980 (Folder 52.39)
  - Grants — Miscellaneous, 1981 (Folder 52.40)
  - Grants — Miscellaneous, 1978-1980 (Folder 52.41)
  - Clyde Griffen Lecture, 1983 (Folder 52.42)
  - Guidelines in case of Campus Disruption, 1970-1971 (Folder 52.43)
  - Handicapped, 1981 (Folder 52.44)
  - Handicapped — Analysis of Facilities, 1978 (Folder 52.45)
  - Hastings Center Conference, 1979-1980 (Folder 52.46)
  - Department of Health, Education and Welfare, 1980 (Folder 52.47)
  - Interview by Martha S. Hennessey, 1982 (Folder 52.48)
  - Herbst/Rousseas Conflict, 1983 (Folder 52.49)
  - Higher Education Resource Services (HERS), 1985 (Folder 52.50)
  - Higher Education Books, 1983-1984 (Folder 52.51)
  - Higher Education Books, 1981-1984 (Folder 52.52)
  - Higher Education — Meeting Training/Conference, 1980-1982 (Folder 52.53)
  - Higher Education Statistics, 1979-1981 (Folder 52.54)
  - VBS’s Confidential File, 1980 (Folder 52.55)
  - Hoffman La Roche, 1981 (Folder 52.56)
  - Holtz, Danuta A. — Confidential, 1983-1984 (Folder 52.57)
  - Hotels (Folder 52.58)
  - Honors (by Department), 1974-1981 (Folder 52.59)
  - Horticulturist Position, 1980 (Folder 52.60)
  - IBM Lunch, 1982-1983 (Folder 52.61)
  - Inter-University Consortium for Educational Computing, Dec 14, 1983 (Folder 52.62)
  - International Education, 1980-1984 (Folder 52.63)
  - Investments, 1981 (Folder 53.1)
  - Iyoya, John, 1982 (Folder 53.2)
  - Meeting with Geoffrey Jehle, Feb 4, 1986 (Folder 53.3)
  - Jewett — Water Damage, 1982 (Folder 53.4)
  - “Kudos”, 1980-1982 (Folder 53.5)
  - Kuhn, Polly — Memos, 1982 (Folder 53.6)
  - Legacies, 1980 (Folder 53.7)
  - Legal File, 1981-1985 (Folder 53.8)
  - Letters to Keep, 1981 (Folder 53.9)
  - Liberal Education Article, 1981-1982 (Folder 53.10)
  - Library Search (Office of the Dean of the College), 1982 (Folder 53.11)
  - Library/Papers, 1983 (Folder 53.12)
  - Lockwood Library — 24 Hour Room, 1983 (Folder 53.13)
  - Long Range Financial Equilibrium for Vassar — Report from VBS, 1982 (Folder 53.14)
  - Maternity Leave, 1981 (Folder 53.15)
  - Advisory Committee — Liberty-Ellis Island Centennial Commission, Oct 1983 (Folder 53.16)
  - Literary Resource Materials, 1981 (Folder 53.17)
  - Lowrie Farm, 1981 (Folder 53.18)
  - Management Negotiations, 1981 (Folder 53.19)
  - Management Programs, 1984-1985 (Folder 53.20)
  - Management Programs, 1981-1982 (Folder 53.21)
  - Management and Higher Education Seminars, 1981-1982 (Folder 53.22)
  - Matta Painting, 1981 (Folder 53.23)
  - Mathew Club Reading Group, 1980-1982 (Folder 53.24)
  - Mathews Minstrels, 1980 (Folder 53.25)
  - Mary McCarthy Visit (Returns), 1982 (Folder 53.26)
  - Mary McCarthy — President’s Distinguished Visitor, Feb 1982 (Folder 53.27)
  - Mary McCarthy/Dixie’s Notes (Folder 53.28)
  - Mary McCarthy — President’s Distinguished Visitor, Feb 1982 (Folder 53.29)
  - Mary McCarthy Papers, 1982-1988 (Folder 53.30)
  - Medallic Art — Brochure, 1980 (Folder 53.31)
  - Marion Tate Memorial Service, Dec 1982 (Folder 53.32)
  - Memorial Services, 1977-1981 (Folder 52.33)
  - Memorial Service — Julia Antolini, May 1981 (Folder 52.34)
  - Memorial Service — Peri Denise Mello, May 1981 (Folder 52.35)
  - Millay Stamp — VBS Remarks, Jul 10, 1981 (Folder 53.36)
  - Millay Stamp day, 1981-1982 (Folder 53.37)
  - Minority Students Project, 1981-1982 (Folder 53.38)
  - Meeting with Miscellany News, Sep 1983 (Folder 53.39)
  - Miscellany News — Correspondence, 1980-1984 (Folder 53.40)
  - Mitchell-Czechoslovak Aquatints, 1982 (Folder 53.41)
  - Sarah Morris, 1981 (Folder 53.42)
  - Muller Solicitation, 1981 (Folder 53.43)
  - National Commission on Higher Education Issues, 1981-1982 (Folder 53.44)
  - National Conference on Women, Economy, and Public Policy, Jun 1984 (Folder 53.45)
  - National Endowment for the Arts (NYS Department of Education), 1980-1981 (Folder 53.46)
  - National Endowment for the Humanities, 1983 (Folder 53.47)
  - National Endowment for the Humanities, 1976-1981 (Folder 53.48)
  - New York City — Liberal Arts Conference, Jun 1981 (Folder 53.49)
  - A — General, 1978-1979 (Folder 53.50)
  - Alternate Meal Plan, 1978-1979 (Folder 53.51)
  - American Association for Higher Education, 1978-1979 (Folder 53.52)
  - Anti-Inflation Program, 1978 (Folder 53.53)
  - Applications for Employment, 1980-1982 (Folder 53.54)
  - Applications for Employment — Vassar College, 1977-1979 (Folder 53.55)
  - Applications for Employment, 1979-1981 (Folder 53.56)
  - Audio Visual Resource Center, 1977-1979 (Folder 53.57)
  - B — General, 1978-1979 (Folder 53.58)
  - Ballet Courses, 1977 (Folder 53.59)
  - Buildings, 1979 (Folder 53.60)
  - C — General, 1977-1979 (Folder 53.61)
  - Calendar Items, 1978-1979 (Folder 53.62)
  - Capital Priorities, 1979 (Folder 53.63)
  - Catalogue, 1977-1978 (Folder 53.64)
  - Choir, 1978 (Folder 54.1)
  - Clearinghouse for Community Based Free Standing Educational Institutions (CBFSEI), 1979 (Folder 54.2)
  - Clearinghouse (CBFSEI), 1980 (Folder 54.3)
  - Clippings, 1980-1981 (Folder 54.4)
  - Clippings, 1979-1980 (Folder 54.5)
  - Clippings, 1978-1979 (Folder 54.6)
  - College Board, 1979 (Folder 54.7)
  - College Board, 1978-1979 (Folder 54.8)
  - Consortium on Financing Higher Education (COFHE), 1977-1978 (Folder 54.9)
  - Consultants, 1979-1980 (Folder 54.10)
  - Convocation, 1978-1979 (Folder 54.11)
  - Cuba Field Trip — Spring 1979, 1978 (Folder 54.12)
  - Cuban Trip — Spring 1978, 1977-1978 (Folder 54.13)
  - D — General, 1978-1979 (Folder 54.14)
  - Damage to Dormitories, 1976-1979 (Folder 54.15)
  - Drugs, 1978 (Folder 54.16)
  - Ecological Field Study, 1976-1978 (Folder 54.17)
  - Energy, 1978-1979 (Folder 54.18)
  - Energy, 1979-1980 (Folder 54.19)
  - Energy, 1980 (Folder 54.20)
  - Entering Students (Class of 1981), 1977 (Folder 54.21)
  - College Entrance Examination Board, 1976-1977 (Folder 54.22)
  - Equestrian Program, 1979-1980 (Folder 54.23)
  - Faculty Activities, 1978-1979 (Folder 54.24)
  - Faculty Appointments and Contracts (Correspondence), 1977-1978 (Folder 54.25)
  - Faculty Appointment Review, 1978 (Folder 54.26)
  - Faculty Appointment and Promotion Procedures, 1978-1979 (Folder 54.27)
  - Faculty Benefits, 1977-1978 (Folder 54.28)
  - Faculty Chairs, 1974-1976 (Folder 54.29)
  - Faculty Club, 1975-1976 (Folder 54.30)
  - Faculty Compensation Figures, 1977-1978 (Folder 54.31)
  - Faculty and Course Evaluation, 1975-1978 (Folder 54.32)
  - Faculty Housing, 1973-1979 (Folder 54.33)
  - Faculty Leaves, 1970-1979 (Folder 54.34)
  - Faculty Reviews, 1977-1979 (Folder 54.35)
  - Faculty Salary and Compensation Study by Department of Economics, 1978 (Folder 54.36)
  - Faculty Salary Budget, 1976-1978 (Folder 54.37)
  - Faculty: Salary Scale, 1976-1977 (Folder 54.38)
  - Faculty: Salary Scale, 1977-1978 (Folder 54.39)
  - Faculty Salary Budget, 1979-1980 (Folder 54.40)
  - Unionization of Faculty, 1973-1976 (Folder 54.41)
  - [Student] — Confidential, 1979 (Folder 54.42)
  - Farm, 1974-1977 (Folder 54.43)
  - Farm — Audubon Study, 1974 (Folder 54.44)
  - The Farm — Margaret Wright’s Report, 1974 (Folder 54.45)
  - Farm — Sasaki Study, 1974-1976 (Folder 55.1)
  - Federal Legislation, 1978-1980 (Folder 55.2)
  - Financial Aid Legislation, 1978 (Folder 55.3)
  - Fitness Trail, 1979 (Folder 55.4)
  - Freshmen Spring Seminar, 1978 (Folder 55.5)
  - Graduate Center, 1970 (Folder 55.6)
  - H — General, 1978-1979 (Folder 55.7)
  - Handicapped, 1977-1979 (Folder 55.8)
  - Department of Health, Education, and Welfare, 1977-1979 (Folder 55.9)
  - Helen Kenyon Lecture, 1978 (Folder 55.10)
  - Higher Education Opportunity Program (HEOP), 1978-1979 (Folder 55.11)
  - Higher Education Statistics/HERS, 1976-1978 (Folder 55.12)
  - Honorary Degrees, 1976-1978 (Folder 55.13)
  - Horticultural Foundation, 1975-1979 (Folder 55.14)
  - House Fellows, 1973-1979 (Folder 55.15)
  - Inaugurations, 1978-1981 (Folder 55.16)
  - Intercultural Center, 1977-1979 (Folder 55.17)
  - Institutional Memberships, 1975-1979 (Folder 55.18)
  - Junior Year Abroad, 1977-1979 (Folder 55.19)
  - L — General, 1978-1979 (Folder 55.20)
  - Leadership Vitality Workshop, 1979 (Folder 55.21)
  - Lectures — General, 1977-1979 (Folder 55.22)
  - Legislation Bills, 1978-1979 (Folder 55.23)
  - Lists — People Connected with Vassar College, 1978-1980 (Folder 55.24)
  - Helen D. Lockwood Essay, 1976-1977 (Folder 55.25)
  - Lockwood Library, 1971-1981 (Folder 55.26)
  - M — General, Jun 1979 (Folder 55.27)
  - Medical School Advising, 1978-1979 (Folder 55.28)
  - Majors’ Committees’ Reports, 1978 (Folder 55.29)
  - Master Plan — State Regents, 1976 (Folder 55.30)
  - Master Plan — State Regents, 1978 (Folder 55.31)
  - Master Plan — State Regents, 1979 (Folder 55.32)
  - Master Plan — State Regents, 1980 (Folder 55.33)
  - Memorial Service (B. Wells), Dec 1978 (Folder 55.34)
  - N — General, 1978-1980 (Folder 55.35)
  - Official Notices, 1978-1980 (Folder 55.36)
  - Office Equipment, 1980 (Folder 55.37)
  - Overview Committee-Notices and Schedule of Meetings, 1978-1979 (Folder 55.38)
  - Overview Committee Meeting Minutes, 1978-1979 (Folder 55.39)
  - Overview Budget, 1978-1979 (Folder 55.40)
  - Parent Loan Plan, 1977-1979 (Folder 56.1)
  - Carolyn Paschal, 1979-1980 (Folder 56.2)
  - Carolyn Paschal, 1979 (Folder 56.3)
  - Director of Communications, 1976-1978 (Folder 56.4)
  - Phi Beta Kappa, 1975-1979 (Folder 56.5)
  - Post Office, 1979 (Folder 56.6)
  - President’s Advisory Group — Members Schedules, 1979 (Folder 56.7)
  - President’s Advisory Meeting, 1978-1979 (Folder 56.8)
  - President’s Information Exchange, 1977-1979 (Folder 56.9)
  - Press Conference, Mar 1981 (Folder 56.10)
  - Private College Financing, 1979 (Folder 56.11)
  - Prizes, 1977-1979 (Folder 56.12)
  - Procedures Manual, 1978-1980 (Folder 56.13)
  - Professional Education (Folder 56.14)
  - Project Second Chance, 1977 (Folder 56.15)
  - Racial Protest, 1979 (Folder 56.16)
  - Racial Tension — Background Material, 1978-1979 (Folder 56.17)
  - Requests for Support, 1978-1979 (Folder 56.18)
  - Retirement, 1978-1979 (Folder 56.19)
  - Sanders Chemistry Building, 1977-1979 (Folder 56.20)
  - Security on Campus, 1979-1981 (Folder 56.21)
  - Search Committees for Institutions Seeking Presidents, Deans, etc., 1978-1980 (Folder 56.22)
  - Seven College Conference of Alumni Associations, 1978-1979 (Folder 56.23)
  - Seven College Career Services/Counseling, 1979 (Folder 56.24)
  - Summer Use of Campus, 1976-1979 (Folder 56.25)
  - Student List — Class of 1982, 1979 (Folder 56.26)
  - Student Lists, 1979-1980 (Folder 56.27)
  - Student Lists, 1978-1979 (Folder 56.28)
  - Student Advisory Committee, 1977-1979 (Folder 56.29)
  - Students’ Afro-American Society (SAS), 1979-1982 (Folder 56.30)
  - Coalition for Social Responsibility, 1978-1981 (Folder 56.31)
  - Student Demonstrations, 1978-1979 (Folder 56.32)
  - Student/Faculty Drug Committee, 1978-1979 (Folder 56.33)
  - Student Entertainment Committee, 1978-1979 (Folder 56.34)
  - Student Fees, 1975-1978 (Folder 56.35)
  - Feminist Union, 1978-1979 (Folder 56.36)
  - Foreign Students, 1975-1980 (Folder 56.37)
  - President’s Invitational Student Forum, 1978 (Folder 56.38)
  - Student Government Association, 1978-1979 (Folder 56.39)
  - Student Interns, 1975-1977 (Folder 56.40)
  - Vassar Jewish Student Union, 1978-1979 (Folder 56.41)
  - Miscellany News — Student Newspaper, 1978-1979 (Folder 56.42)
  - Nerd Organization, 1978 (Folder 56.43)
  - Nutshell Problem, 1978-1979 (Folder 56.44)
  - Officers — Student for, 1979-1980 (Folder 56.45)
  - Freshmen Orientation, 1977-1979 (Folder 56.46)
  - New Student Orientation, 1979 (Folder 56.47)
  - Probation Lists (Confidential), 1978-1981 (Folder 56.48)
  - Academic Panel Appeal — [Student] (Confidential), 1978-1980 (Folder 56.49)
  - Student Press, 1978-1979 (Folder 56.50)
  - Student Schedules, 1979 (Folder 56.51)
  - Student Senate, 1977-1978 (Folder 56.52)
  - Students/Special Interests Lists, 1979 (Folder 56.53)
  - Syllabus, 1980 (Folder 56.54)
  - Tuition, 1978-1980 (Folder 56.55)
  - Unscrewed, 1978-1981 (Folder 56.56)
  - Student Radio Station WVKR, 1979-1981 (Folder 56.57)
  - Students (Self Study), 1978-1979 (Folder 56.58)
  - A — Students, 1976-1981 (Folder 56.59)
  - B — Students, 1978-1981 (Folder 56.60)
  - C — Students, 1979-1981 (Folder 57.1)
  - [Student] — Confidential, 1981 (Folder 57.2)
  - D — Students, 1979-1981 (Folder 57.3)
  - E — Students, 1978-1981 (Folder 57.4)
  - F — Students, 1979-1981 (Folder 57.5)
  - G — Students, 1979-1981 (Folder 57.6)
  - H — Students, 1979-1981 (Folder 57.7)
  - I — Students, 1980 (Folder 57.8)
  - J — Students, 1979-1980 (Folder 57.9)
  - K — Students, 1978-1981 (Folder 57.10)
  - L — Students, 1978-1981 (Folder 57.11)
  - M — Students, 1978-1981 (Folder 57.12)
  - N — Students, 1980 (Folder 57.13)
  - O — Students, 1978-1981 (Folder 57.14)
  - P — Students, 1978-1981 (Folder 57.15)
  - R — Students, 1977-1981 (Folder 57.16)
  - S — Students, 1979-1981 (Folder 57.17)
  - T — Students, 1978-1981 (Folder 57.18)
  - U-V — Students, 1979-1980 (Folder 57.19)
  - Vaid, Urvashi — Recommendation, 1979 (Folder 57.20)
  - W — Students, 1979-1981 (Folder 57.21)
  - X-Y-Z — Students, 1980 (Folder 57.22)
  - Town/Government, 1978-1979 (Folder 57.23)
  - Travel Plans, 1978-1980 (Folder 57.24)
  - Union Contract, 1976-1979 (Folder 57.25)
  - Urban Center, 1976-1979 (Folder 57.26)
  - Urban Center for Africana Studies, 1978-1980 (Folder 57.27)
  - Vacancies, 1980-1982 (Folder 57.28)
  - Vassar Today, 1976-1979 (Folder 57.29)
  - Workshop on Science and Ethics, 1978 (Folder 57.30)
  - Woodstock, 1977-1979 (Folder 57.31)
  - Unscrewed — Newspaper, 1981-1985 (Folder 57.32)
  - Unscrewed — Newspaper, 1983 (Folder 57.33)
  - Vassar — General, 1980 (Folder 57.34)
  - Vacancy, 1981-1985 (Folder 57.35)
  - Vacancy, 1983 (Folder 57.36)
  - Vacation Schedules, 1983 (Folder 57.37)
  - Vacation Schedules, 1978-1981 (Folder 57.38)
  - Vassar Calendar, 1980-1983 (Folder 57.39)
  - Vassar Calendar, 1979-1980 (Folder 57.40)
  - Vassar College Statistics and Facts, 1980 (Folder 57.41)
  - Vassar History/Archives, 1980 (Folder 57.42)
  - Vassar-Wesleyan Semester in Madrid, 1980 (Folder 57.43)
  - Mary Villard Retirement Party, May 15, 1981 (Folder 57.44)
  - Vishniac, 1985 (Folder 57.45)
  - Walker Field House Dedication, 1982-1984 (Folder 57.46)
  - Weird, 1982-1985 (Folder 57.47)
  - Weird, 1981-1983 (Folder 57.48)
  - Weird, 1980 (Folder 57.49)
  - West Point (US Military Academy) — Invitation to Lunch/Game, 1983 (Folder 57.50)
  - Inauguration of Keohane at Wellesley, Sep 18, 1981 (Folder 57.51)
  - Eudora Welty, 1980-1981 (Folder 57.52)
  - Non-Western Studies, 1984 (Folder 57.53)
  - Women in Higher Education, 1984 (Folder 57.54)
  - Women — General, 1981-1984 (Folder 57.55)
  - Women’s Issues, 1979 (Folder 57.56)
  - Women’s Issues, 1980 (Folder 57.57)
  - Women’s Issues, 1981 (Folder 57.58)
  - Women in Higher Education, 1980 (Folder 57.59)
  - Women in Higher Education, 1981 (Folder 57.60)
  - “Women”, 1981-1982 (Folder 57.61)
  - Women — Awards, 1981 (Folder 57.62)
  - Women and Financing Higher Education, 1981 (Folder 57.63)
  - Women’s Group, Sep 1983 (Folder 57.64)
  - Women on Vassar Faculty, 1976-1983 (Folder 57.65)
  - Women’s Studies, 1977-1980 (Folder 57.66)
  - Women’s Studies, 1981 (Folder 57.67)
  - Work After College Seminar, 1979 (Folder 58.1)
  - EFS (Vassar Farm), 1973-1983; (17 folders) (Folders 58.2-58.18)
  - Students: Individual Requests, 1983-1984 (Folder 58.19)
  - Students: Individual Requests, 1982-1983 (Folder 58.20)
  - Open Office Hours for Students, 1982-1983 (Folder 58.21)
  - Students: Open Office Hours — Sign-in Sheets, 1981-1982 (Folder 58.22)
  - Students: Open Office Hours, 1980-1981 (Folder 58.23)
  - Special Students, 1983 (Folder 58.24)
  - Students: SAS Concerns, 1980-1982 (Folder 58.25)
  - Students: SAS Concerns, 1979 (Folder 58.26)
  - V.S.A. Deficit, 1979 (Folder 58.27)
  - Vassar Student Association (VSA) — General, 1980-1985 (Folder 58.28)
  - Vassar Student Association — Minutes of Meetings, 1980-1981 (Folder 58.29)
  - Student Wage Committee, 1983 (Folder 58.30)
  - Students: (VSA President) Herman Farrell, 1982-1983 (Folder 58.31)
  - Students: [Student] (Confidential), 1982 (Folder 58.32)
  - Students: Activities (General), 1979-1984 (Folder 58.33)
  - Students: (VSA President) Maurice Edelson, 1983-1984 (Folder 58.34)
  - Students: [Student] (Confidential), 1982 (Folder 58.35)
  - Subscriptions, 1983-1984 (Folder 58.36)
  - Plans for Second Semester (DMS), 1983 (Folder 58.37)
  - Summer Institute on Computers, 1982 (Folder 58.38)
  - Vassar Summer Programs, 1982-1985 (Folder 58.39)
  - Summer Schedules, 1982 (Folder 58.40)
  - Summer Use of Campus, 1980-1984 (Folder 58.41)
  - Sunrise Matter, 1983 (Folder 58.42)
  - Sunset Lake, 1982 (Folder 58.43)
  - T — General, 1978-1982 (Folder 58.44)
  - Tampered Mail — VBS, 1982 (Folder 58.45)
  - Nancy Teeters Lecture, 1980 (Folder 58.46)
  - Telephones, 1980 (Folder 58.47)
  - Testing, 1979-1981 (Folder 58.48)
  - Thank-You Notes, 1984-1986 (Folder 58.49)
  - Thank-You Notes, 1983-1984 (Folder 58.50)
  - Thank-You Notes, 1981-1985 (Folder 58.51)
  - TIAA-CREF — Retirement Plan, 1984 (Folder 58.52)
  - TIAA-CREF, 1975-1979 (Folder 58.53)
  - “Today” Show Interview with Phil Donohue — VBS, 1980 (Folder 58.54)
  - Tuition Remission Program, 1981 (Folder 58.55)
  - Twenty College Program, 1981 (Folder 58.56)
  - U/V — General, 1978-1980 (Folder 58.57)
  - U.W. Campaign Kickoff Breakfast at Vassar, Sep 1984 (Folder 58.58)
  - United Way, 1984-1986 (Folder 58.59)
  - United Way, 1985 (Folder 58.60)
  - Dutchess County United Way, 1983-1985 (Folder 58.61)
  - United Way of Dutchess County, 1982-1983 (Folder 58.62)
  - United Way, 1981-1982 (Folder 58.63)
  - United Way, 1975-1981 (Folder 58.64)
  - Mellon Reports — C. Buntting, 1982 (Folder 58.65)
  - Mellon Reports, 1982 (Folder 58.66)
  - Mellon Grant (Study by Department), 1980 (Folder 58.67)
  - Mellon, 1982 (Folder 58.68)
  - Mellon Awardees List, 1979-1981 (Folder 59.1)
  - Mellon Foundation — Old File, 1976-1981 (Folder 59.2)
  - Notes of Regret, 1985-1986 (Folder 59.3)
  - Mellon — Fall, 1983-1986 (Folder 59.4)
  - Mellon — Spring, 1986 (Folder 59.5)
  - Mellon — Fall, 1986 (Folder 59.6)
  - Mellon — Spring, 1987 (Folder 59.7)
  - Annual Reports, 1987 (Folder 59.8)
  - Annual Report — Press and Information Office and Vice President of Student Affairs, 1986-1988 (Folder 59.9)
  - Annual Reports, 1985 (Folder 59.10)
  - Annual Reports, 1985 (Folder 59.11)
  - Annual Reports, 1985 (Folder 59.12)
  - Parks, Robert, 1984 (Folder 59.13)
  - De Maria, Robert/Christensen, Carol, 1984 (Folder 59.14)
  - Feroe, John, 1984 (Folder 59.15)
  - Gounaris, Anne, 1984 (Folder 59.16)
  - Harris, Ben/Leonard, Eileen, 1984 (Folder 59.17)
  - Jehle, Geoffrey, 1984 (Folder 59.18)
  - Rossi, Miriam, 1984 (Folder 59.19)
  - Travel, Morton, 1984 (Folder 59.20)
  - Computer Literacy, 1983-1984 (Folder 59.21)
  - Mellon Grants, 1980 (Folder 59.22)
  - Mellon/Sloan Grants Guidelines, 1983 (Folder 59.23)
  - Mellon/Sloan — Course Outlines, 1983-1984 (Folder 59.24)
  - Sloan Grants — Extra Copies, 1983 (Folder 59.25)
  - Mellon Grants — List of Grants, 1984 (Folder 59.26)
  - Sloan Grants — List of Grants, 1984 (Folder 59.27)
  - Sloan Grants — Correspondence, 1983-1984 (Folder 59.28)
  - Mellon Grants — Extra Copies, 1983-1984 (Folder 59.29)
  - Mellon Grants — Recommendations to VBS, 1983 (Folder 59.30)
  - Computer Literacy Program, 1982-1983 (Folder 59.31)
  - Sloan Grants — Budget, 1983-1984 (Folder 59.32)
  - President Smith — Mellon Grants, 1984 (Folder 59.33)
  - Mellon Grants — Budget, 1984 (Folder 59.34)
  - Bergon, Frank, 1983-1984 (Folder 59.35)
  - Brown, D. B., 1984 (Folder 59.36)
  - De Maria, Robert, 1984 (Folder 59.37)
  - Gournaris, Anne, 1983-1984 (Folder 59.38)
  - Kaurouma, Patricia, 1983-1984 (Folder 59.39)
  - Reno, Christine, 1983-1984 (Folder 59.40)
  - Stillman, Peters, 1983-1984 (Folder 59.41)
  - Mellon/Sloan Grants, 1983-1984 (Folder 59.42)
  - Mellon/Sloan Grants — Chrono, 1983-1984 (Folder 59.43)
  - Mellon Grants — Correspondence, 1983-1984 (Folder 59.44)
  - Bergon, Frank/Cormiter, Susan, 1983-1984 (Folder 60.1)
  - Chromey, Frederick, 1983-1984 (Folder 60.2)
  - Harris, Ben, 1983 (Folder 60.3)
  - Ide, Nancy M. (2), 1983-1984 (Folder 60.4)
  - Johnson, L.L./Schlessman, M., 1983-1985 (Folder 60.5)
  - Lockwood, Annea, 1983-1984 (Folder 60.6)
  - Herbst, Lawrence, 1983-1984 (Folder 60.7)
  - Pearl, Alexander, 1983-1984 (Folder 60.8)
  - Rossi, Miriam, 1983-1984 (Folder 60.9)
  - Schlessman, Mark, 1983-1984 (Folder 60.10)
  - Stillman, Peter, 1983-1984 (Folder 60.11)
  - Tavel, Morton, 1983-1984 (Folder 60.12)
  - Badanes, Jerome, 1984 (Folder 60.13)
  - Cook, Ray, 1984 (Folder 60.14)
  - Cormier, Susan, 1984 (Folder 60.15)
  - Cox, David, 1984 (Folder 60.16)
  - Darlington, Beth, 1984 (Folder 60.17)
  - Gray, Obika, 1984 (Folder 60.18)
  - Johnson, L. Lewis, 1984 (Folder 60.19)
  - Kerr, Cynthia, 1984 (Folder 60.20)
  - Mitchell, Rebecca, 1984 (Folder 60.21)
  - Mucci, Joseph, 1984 (Folder 60.22)
  - Mellon Group Request, 1982-1983 (Folder 60.23)
  - Bickerstaff, Joyce, 1982-1983 (Folder 60.24)
  - Fischel, Evelyn, 1982-1983 (Folder 60.25)
  - Fisher, Cynthia, 1983-1984 (Folder 60.26)
  - Hammond, Christina, 1982-1983 (Folder 60.27)
  - Johnson, Shirley B., 1982-1983 (Folder 60.28)
  - Kalin, Jesse, 1982-1983 (Folder 60.29)
  - McCleary, John, 1982-1984 (Folder 60.30)
  - Silverman, Sondra, 1982-1983 (Folder 60.31)
  - Spicer, Donald Z., 1982-1984 (Folder 60.32)
  - Balmuth, Jeremy, 1983 (Folder 60.33)
  - Kennett, David A., 1983 (Folder 60.34)
  - Livingston, Ken, 1983 (Folder 60.35)
  - Lun, William/Economics Department, 1983-1984 (Folder 60.36)
  - Mamiya, Lawrence H., 1983 (Folder 60.37)
  - Moore, Deborah D., 1982-1983 (Folder 60.38)
  - Pin, E. Jean, 1982-1983 (Folder 60.39)
  - Schlessman, Mark A., 1983 (Folder 60.40)
  - Shanley, Mary L., 1982-1983 (Folder 60.41)
  - Spicer, Donald Z., 1983 (Folder 60.42)
  - Ide, Nancy M., 1983 (Folder 60.43)
  - Stillman, Peter G., 1983 (Folder 60.44)
  - Williams, Donald B., 1982-1983 (Folder 60.45)
  - Mellon Grant — Budget, 1982-1984 (Folder 60.46)
  - Mellon Grant — Guidelines, 1982 (Folder 60.47)
  - Second Round Applications, 1982-1983 (Folder 60.48)
  - Mellon Grant — Chrono – C Bunting/P. Johnson, 1982-1983 (Folder 60.49)
  - Mellon Grant — Correspondence, 1982-1983 (Folder 60.50)
  - Mellon Grant — Recommendations to VBS, 1982-1983 (Folder 60.51)
  - Mellon Grant — List of Grants, 1982 (Folder 60.52)
  - Mellon Grant — Extra Copies, 1982-1983 (Folder 60.53)
  - Mellon/Sloan Grants, 1983-1986 (Folder 60.54)
  - Mellon Committee Correspondence, 1982-1983 (Folder 60.55)
  - Recommendations to VBS from Mellon Committee, 1982 (Folder 60.56)
  - Mellon Committee Chrono — Pat Tyler, 1981-1982 (Folder 60.57)
  - Mellon Grant — Budget, 1982-1983 (Folder 60.58)
  - Applications Needing Review, 1979-1980 (Folder 60.59)
  - Murray, Michael, 1982 (Folder 60.60)
  - Armstrong, James, 1982-1983 (Folder 60.61)
  - Gifford, William, 1982-1983 (Folder 60.62)
  - Harris, Benjamin, 1982-1983 (Folder 60.63)